Finding Aid for Yale Kamisar Papers
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Research Topical Files, 2003-2004; 14. 4 linear feet
  - C-D
    - Dressler, Joshua, 1988-1994 (Box 5)
    - Dripps, Donald A., 1985-1990 (Box 5)
    - Drug Testing Drafts and Articles, 1986-1987 (Box 5)
    - Drugs
      - AFL-CIO v. Meese, 1985 (Box 5)
      - Lovvorn v. City of Chattanooga, undated (Box 5)
      - Penny v. Kennedy, undated (Box 5)
      - Testing, 1987 (Box 5)
  - E-H
    - Eagleton, Thomas F., 1982 (Box 6)
    - Easterbrook, Frank, 1983-1994 (Box 6)
    - Edelman, Peter, 1988 (Box 6)
    - Edwards, Harry T., 1981-2003 (Box 6)
    - Eisenberg, Melvin A., 1985 (Box 6)
    - Eisner, Brian, 1983 (Box 6)
    - Elderly People, Treatment of, 1993 (Box 6)
    - Electronic Eavesdropping, 1988 (Box 6)
    - Emanuel, Ezekiel, undated (Box 6)
    - Emanuel, Linda, 1997 (Box 6)
    - Emerson, Ken, 1986-1988 (Box 6)
    - Encyclopedia Americana, 1972-1973 (Box 6)
    - Encyclopedia Britannica, 1990 (Box 6)
    - Encyclopedia of Crime and Justice, 1981 (Box 6)
    - Encyclopedia of Criminology, 1992-1994 (Box 6)
    - Encyclopedia of the American Constitution, 1983-1985 (Box 6)
    - English Law, 1979 (Box 6)
    - Enker, Arnold, 1980-1989 (Box 6)
    - Epstein, Richard, 1994-1997 (Box 6)
    - Erickson, William H., 1982-1987 (Box 6)
    - Ervin, Sam J., Jr., 1983 (Box 6)
    - Erwin, Mary, 1982-1988 (Box 6)
    - Escobedo, Danny, 1974; 1985 (Box 6)
    - Euthanasia
      - American, 1983 (Box 6)
      - Baby Jane Doe, 1984; 2 folders (Box 6)
      - British, 1970; 1976 (Box 6)
      - Brophy, Paul, 1986 (Box 6)
      - Cassette Tapes, undated (Box 6)
      - Children, 1979-1981 (Box 6)
      - Education Programs, 1972-1980 (Box 6)
      - General, 1974-1990; 1996; 9 folders (Box 6)
      - Harvard Medical School, 1974 (Box 6)
      - Medical Economics, 1977 (Box 6)
      - Mercy-killing Article, 1958; 1973; 2 folders (Box 6)
      - Mitchell Lecture (SUNY-Buffalo), 1978 (Box 6)
      - New York Cases, 1979-1985 (Box 6)
      - Papers, 1979 (Box 6)
      - Quinlan's Guardians, 1977; 1984 (Box 6)
      - Thomas, Julia, 1979 (Box 6)
    - Everett, Robinson O., 1981-1990 (Box 6)
    - Everson, Nanette, 1987 (Box 6)
    - Evolution, 1981-1982 (Box 6)
    - Examination Memos, 1989-1992; 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Exclusionary Rule, 1972-1993 (Box 7)
    - Expert Witnesses, 1988 (Box 7)
    - Externships, 1988; 1996; 3 folders (Box 7)
    - Extradition, 1984 (Box 7)
    - Federalist Society, 1988 (Box 7)
    - Fee Forfeiture, 1989 (Box 7)
    - Fein, Bruce, 1972; 1994 (Box 7)
    - Felony Murder, 1980; 1989 (Box 7)
    - Feminism, 1987; 1989 (Box 7)
    - Fine, Sidney, 1983-1988 (Box 7)
    - Finkin, Matthew, 1981-1982 (Box 7)
    - Fitzgerald, Richard J., 1985 (Box 7)
    - Fitzhugh, Josh, 1980 (Box 7)
    - Flag Burning, 1989-1990 (Box 7)
    - Flaum, Joel M., undated (Box 7)
    - Fleming, Robben W., 1985 (Box 7)
    - Fletcher, Betty, 1989 (Box 7)
    - Fletcher, George P., 1979 (Box 7)
    - Fogelberg, Paul A., 1981 (Box 7)
    - Fordham University, 1981 (Box 7)
    - Forrester, Ray, 1964 (Box 7)
    - Fortas, Abe, 1968; 1983 (Box 7)
    - Foundation Press, 1988-1993 (Box 7)
    - Fourth Amendment, 1988-1989 (Box 7)
    - Fox, Brother Joseph Charles, 1979-1983 (Box 7)
    - Frank, John P., 1984-1991 (Box 7)
    - Frankel, Marvin E., 1990 (Box 7)
    - Freedman, Nancy, 1983 (Box 7)
    - Freedom of Speech, 1989-1991 (Box 7)
    - Freund, Paul A., undated (Box 7)
    - Frey, Andrew, 1983-1987 (Box 7)
    - Fried, Charles, 1985-1987 (Box 7)
    - Friedlander, Betty, 1964 (Box 7)
    - Friedman, Jane, 1970-1973 (Box 7)
    - Friedman, Leon, 1985 (Box 7)
    - Friendly, Henry, 1986 (Box 7)
    - Frievogel, Bill, 1990 (Box 7)
    - Frye, Billy E., 1982 (Box 7)
    - Fyfe, James, J., 1983 (Box 7)
    - Gangi, William, 1985-1986 (Box 7)
    - Garland Publishing Company, 1995 (Box 7)
    - Garrow, David, 1995 (Box 7)
    - Garver, Newton, 1984 (Box 7)
    - Gelfand, Gregory, 1985-1986 (Box 7)
    - Georgetown University Press, 1993 (Box 7)
    - Gesell, Gerhard A., 1985 (Box 7)
    - Giarratano, Joseph, 1990 (Box 7)
    - Gideon v. Wainwright, 1988-1991 (Box 7)
    - Gillers, Stephen, 1981-1982 (Box 7)
    - Gilman, Gregg, undated (Box 7)
    - Ginsberg, Douglas, 1987 (Box 7)
    - Ginsburg, Ruth Bader, 1981-1987 (Box 7)
    - Godbold, John, 1981 (Box 7)
    - Gold, Joel, 1989 (Box 7)
    - Goldberg, Howard, 1989-1996 (Box 7)
    - Goldberg v. Kelly, undated (Box 7)
    - Goldman, Henry F., 1990 (Box 7)
    - Goldsmith, Michael, 1990 (Box 7)
    - Goldsmith, Stephen, 1983 (Box 7)
    - Goldstein, Abraham, 1982 (Box 7)
    - Goldstein, Joseph, 1959 (Box 7)
    - Goldstock, Ronald, 1992 (Box 7)
    - Gomez, Carlos, 1992; 1995 (Box 7)
    - Goodman, Elliott I., 1982-1985 (Box 7)
    - Goodpaster, Gary S., 1982; 1990 (Box 7)
    - Gordon, Diana R., 1981 (Box 7)
    - Gordan, Virginia, 1987-1989 (Box 7)
    - Gottlieb and Schwartz, 1983 (Box 7)
    - Gould, Ron, 1995-2002 (Box 7)
    - Graduate Program, 1988-1989; 1988 (Box 7)
    - Graduation Speeches, 1980-1999 (Box 7)
    - Graglia, Lino A., 1987 (Box 7)
    - Graham, Michael, undated (Box 7)
    - Grammar, English, 1984 (Box 7)
    - Grand Juries, 1985-1990 (Box 7)
    - Granelli, James S., 1982 (Box 7)
    - Grano, Joseph D., 1993-2000 (Box 7)
    - Grants, 1986-1998 (Box 7)
    - Greene, Abner, 1988-1990 (Box 7)
    - Greenfield, Meg, 1979-1987 (Box 7)
    - Greenhalgh, William, 1982 (Box 7)
    - Greenhouse, Linda, 1988-1990 (Box 7)
    - Greenwood Publishing, 2002 (Box 7)
    - Griffith, Charles, 1985 (Box 7)
    - Grisez, Germain, 1989 (Box 7)
    - Griswold, Erwin N., 1980-1989 (Box 7)
    - Grossman, Steven P., 1983 (Box 7)
    - Gryphon Editions, Inc., 1988-1999 (Box 7)
    - Guggenheim Foundation, 1977-1991 (Box 7)
    - Gun Control, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Gunther, Gerald, 1995 (Box 7)
    - Haas, Kenneth, 1990 (Box 7)
    - Haas, Margaret, 1980 (Box 7)
    - Habeas Corpus, 1989-1993 (Box 7)
    - Haddad, James, 1983-1989 (Box 7)
    - Hale, Jim, 1987-1995 (Box 7)
    - Hall, John Wesley, 1984 (Box 8)
    - Hall, Search and Seizure, 1988 (Box 8)
    - Hallmark, Steve, 1983 (Box 8)
    - Hanscom, C.B., 1963 (Box 8)
    - Harris, Jean, 1981 (Box 8)
    - Hart Lectures, 1988 (Box 8)
    - Harvard Journal, 2002 (Box 8)
    - Harvard Law Record, 1983 (Box 8)
    - Harvard Law Review, 1960-1992 (Box 8)
    - Harvard Law Review Book Review, 1963 (Box 8)
    - Hastings Center, 1993-2000 (Box 8)
    - Hastings Constitutional Law Quarterly, 1993-1994 (Box 8)
    - Hatch, Orrin, 1987 (Box 8)
    - Hate Mail, 1986 (Box 8)
    - Hawkland, William D., 1982 (Box 8)
    - Hay, Peter, 1984-1984 (Box 8)
    - Hays, Paul, 1962-1963 (Box 8)
    - Hazard, Geoffrey C., 1984 (Box 8)
    - Heffernan, William C., 1982 (Box 8)
    - Hellerstein, William, 1991 (Box 8)
    - Hellman, Arthur D., 1983 (Box 8)
    - Hemlock Society, 1985-1987 (Box 8)
    - Henkin, Louis, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Hennings, Thomas, C., Jr., 1959-1960 (Box 8)
    - Hentoff, Nat, 1991-1994 (Box 8)
    - Herbert v. Lando, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
    - Herman, Lawrence, 1988 (Box 8)
    - Herpel, Stefan, 1990-1996 (Box 8)
    - Herrmann, Daniel, 1978-1990 (Box 8)
    - Heymann, Philip B., 1987 (Box 8)
    - Hill and Wang, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Hillman, Douglas, 1982-1987 (Box 8)
    - Hillsdale College, 1993 (Box 8)
    - Hines, Laura, 1996 (Box 8)
    - Hingson, John Henry, 1989 (Box 8)
    - Hiss, Donald, 1983 (Box 8)
    - Hodson Lectures, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Hoelzel, William E., 1985-1986 (Box 8)
    - Holmes, Kenneth, 1990 (Box 8)
    - Hommel, Penny, 1990 (Box 8)
    - Hook, Sidney, 1989 (Box 8)
    - Horsky, Charles A., 1989-1997 (Box 8)
    - Horwitz, Morton, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Houston Law Center, University of, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Howard, A.E. Dick, 1981-1987 (Box 8)
    - Howe, Scott, 1984 (Box 8)
    - Hoyt, Jane, 1984-1985 (Box 8)
    - Hrones, Stephen, 1987 (Box 8)
    - Hufstedler, Shirley M., 1983 (Box 8)
    - Hughes Estate, 1983 (Box 8)
    - Humor, 1958 (Box 8)
    - Hutchinson, Dennis, 1982-1983 (Box 8)
  - I-M
    - I.C.L.E. (Institute of Continuing Legal Education), 1982-1987 (Box 8)
    - Illinois Debate (Exclusionary Rule), 1981 (Box 8)
    - Illinois, University of, 1990-1993 (Box 8)
    - Imwinkelried, Ed, 1989 (Box 8)
    - Inbau, Fred, 1991 (Box 8)
    - Income Tax, 1974-1977 (Box 8)
    - Independent Prosecutor, 1988 (Box 8)
    - Ingber, Stanley, 1987 (Box 8)
    - Insurance, 1976 (Box 8)
    - Insanity, 1992 (Box 8)
    - Integration, 1987 (Box 8)
    - Israel, Jerry, 1980-1994 (Box 8)
    - Jaffe, Peter, 1992 (Box 8)
    - Japan Conference (Miyazawa), 1990 (Box 8)
    - Japanese Scholars, 1980-1985 (Box 8)
    - Jensen, D. Lowell, 1986 (Box 8)
    - Jewish Law Review, 1985 (Box 8)
    - Jewish Law Students' Association, 1984 (Box 8)
    - Jews, 1984 (Box 8)
    - John Jay College, 1978-1982 (Box 8)
    - John Marshall Fellowship, 1990 (Box 8)
    - Johnson, Phillip E., 1983-1987 (Box 8)
    - Johnson, Sheri Lynn, 1985 (Box 8)
    - Johnston, Thomas V., 1984 (Box 8)
    - Jordan, Ellen R., 1993 (Box 8)
    - Josephson, Michael S., 1981-1987 (Box 8)
    - Journal of Criminal Law and Criminology, 1985 (Box 8)
    - Journalism Seminar, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Judges, 1979-1981 (Box 8)
    - Judges' Journal, 1972-1974 (Box 8)
    - Judicature, 1977-1982 (Box 8)
    - Judicial Clerkships, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Kadish, Sanford, 1992-1995 (Box 8)
    - Kagan, Robert, 1983 (Box 8)
    - Kahn, Laurence M., 1981 (Box 8)
    - Kalven, Harry, Jr., 1959-1962 (Box 8)
    - Kamisar, Christine, 1997-1998 (Box 8)
    - Kamisar, Yale
      - Distinguished Professorship, 1992-1993 (Box 8)
      - Profile, 1963; 1990-1993 (Box 8)
    - Kass, Leon R., 1994-1996 (Box 8)
    - Katz, Lewis R., 1981-1984 (Box 8)
    - Keenan, John, 1975-1977 (Box 9)
    - Keith, Damon, 1984 (Box 9)
    - Kennedy, Anthony, 1987-1988 (Box 9)
    - Kennedy, Edward M., 1978 (Box 9)
    - Kennedy, Randall, 1987-1996 (Box 9)
    - Kerby, Philip, 1982 (Box 9)
    - Kerper Book, 1975-1977 (Box 9)
    - Killebrew, 1981 (Box 9)
    - King, Nancy, 1987-1996 (Box 9)
    - Kirkendall, John, 1990 (Box 9)
    - Kirkpatrick, Laird, 1990 (Box 9)
    - Kirwin, Kenneth, 1972 (Box 9)
    - Klipper, Michael, 1982 (Box 9)
    - Knauss, Rob, 1981 (Box 9)
    - Knutson, Oscar, 1963 (Box 9)
    - Koenig, Dorean M., 1984-1992 (Box 9)
    - Koop, C. Everett (Institute), 1995 (Box 9)
    - Korn, Harold, 1961 (Box 9)
    - Kozinski, Alex, 1992 (Box 9)
    - Kramer, Victor, 1997 (Box 9)
    - Krantz, Sheldon, 1984 (Box 9)
    - Krash, Abe, 1962-1963; 1985 (Box 9)
    - Krauss, Stanton D., 1987-1994 (Box 9)
    - Krauthammer, Charles, 1993 (Box 9)
    - Kroll, Barry L., 1983 (Box 9)
    - Kugler, Gordon, 1991-1992 (Box 9)
    - Kuh, Richard H., 1983 (Box 9)
    - Kurland, Paul, 1960-1962 (Box 9)
    - LaFave, William, 1982-1993; 4 folders (Box 9)
    - Landau, Jack C., 1979 (Box 9)
    - Landynski, Jacob, 1961 (Box 9)
    - Langley, Keith, 1990 (Box 9)
    - Langrock, Peter F., 1983-1990 (Box 9)
    - Larsen, Jan, 1972-1973 (Box 9)
    - Larson, Edward, 1994; undated (Box 9)
    - Lasson, Nelson B., 1970 (Box 9)
    - Lauter, David, 1987 (Box 9)
    - Law Firms
      - 1984 (Box 9)
      - Ann Arbor, 1985 (Box 9)
    - Law Quadrangle Notes, 1986-1997; 3 folders (Box 9)
    - Law Reprints (reel-to-reel tape), undated (Box 9)
    - Law Review, Michigan
      - General, 1983-1995 (Box 9)
      - Letters, 1971-1976 (Box 9)
    - Law School
      - Current, 1987-1988 (Box 9)
      - Faculty, 1988 (Box 9)
      - Independent Studies, 1988 (Box 9)
      - Leading Prospects, 1988 (Box 9)
      - University of Michigan, 1972-1991 (Box 9)
    - Lawson, Edward C., 1983 (Box 9)
    - Lawyers, 1988-1993 (Box 9)
    - Lawyers Fees, 1988 (Box 9)
    - Leading Cases, 1988 (Box 9)
    - Lectures at Other Schools, 1980-1981 (Box 9)
    - Lederman, Eli, 1982-1983 (Box 9)
    - Lee, Rex E., 1982-1985 (Box 9)
    - Legal Aid, 1985-1988 (Box 9)
    - Legal Aid Society, 1979-1989 (Box 9)
    - Legal Classics Library, 1985-1988 (Box 9)
    - Legal Ethics, 1988-1992 (Box 9)
    - Legal Times, 1993 (Box 9)
    - Legal Writing, undated (Box 9)
    - Legislative Veto, 1983 (Box 9)
    - Lehman, Jeffrey, 1977-1998 (Box 9)
    - Leibowitz, Arnold H., 1979-1981 (Box 9)
    - Leitman, Bruce T., 1983-1999 (Box 9)
    - Lempert, Richard, undated (Box 9)
    - Lent, Berkeley, 1983 (Box 9)
    - Leo, Richard, 1996 (Box 9)
    - Leon & Sheppard, 1984 (Box 9)
    - Lesser, Stanley, C., 1985; 1999 (Box 9)
    - Leventhal Letter, 1978 (Box 9)
    - Levin, A. Leo, 1983 (Box 9)
    - Levin, Charles L., 1980 (Box 9)
    - Levine, Randi, 1982 (Box 9)
    - Levitt, Daniel P., 1984 (Box 9)
    - Levy, Deborah, 1989-1992 (Box 9)
    - Levy, Leonard W., 1969; 1979-1989 (Box 9)
    - Lewis, Anthony, 1964-1989 (Box 9)
    - Libner, Robert, 1993 (Box 10)
    - Library
      - Committee, 1975-1993 (Box 10)
      - Materials, 1975 (Box 10)
      - Memorandum, 1994-1995 (Box 10)
      - Searches, 1987 (Box 10)
    - Lichtman, Jay L., 1982-1985 (Box 10)
    - Lieberman, Jethro, 1986-1993 (Box 10)
    - Lie Detectors, 1982-1997 (Box 10)
    - Lieb, Peter, 1984 (Box 10)
    - Life, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
    - Life, Right to, 1980-1986 (Box 10)
    - Life Times, 1979-1991 (Box 10)
    - Linacre Center, 1993 (Box 10)
    - Linde, Hans A., 1981-1984 (Box 10)
    - Line-Up, 1984 (Box 10)
    - Linton, Paul, 1994; 1996 (Box 10)
    - Lipset, Harold, 1960-1962 (Box 10)
    - Liss, Jeffrey, F., 1982-1983 (Box 10)
    - Little Brown & Company, 1992-1993 (Box 10)
    - Lockhart, William B., 1985-1989 (Box 10)
    - Loeb, Alan, 1985 (Box 10)
    - Loewy, Arnold, 1982 (Box 10)
    - London Times, 1982 (Box 10)
    - Look, 1979 (Box 10)
    - LoPrete, James, 1993 (Box 10)
    - Los Angeles Times, 1990-1996 (Box 10)
    - Louisiana State University, 1984-1985 (Box 10)
    - Low, Charlotte, 1980-1987 (Box 10)
    - Lupu, Ira C., undated (Box 10)
    - Lutheran General Hospital, 1996 (Box 10)
    - Lynn, Joanne, 1996 (Box 10)
    - MacDonald Case, 1982 (Box 10)
    - MacKenzie, John P., 1985-1989 (Box 10)
    - MacKinnon George, 1983-1987 (Box 10)
    - MacLin, Tracey, 1985-1997 (Box 10)
    - MacMillan Publishing Company, 1992; 1997 (Box 10)
    - MacNeil-Lehrer News Hour, 1989-1990 (Box 10)
    - Mail Fraud, 1987 (Box 10)
    - Mann, Jim, 1982 (Box 10)
    - Manne, Neal, 1987 (Box 10)
    - Marcus, Paul, 1987 (Box 10)
    - Margolick, David, 1987-1993 (Box 10)
    - Margolin, Ephraim, 1985-1997 (Box 10)
    - Margolis, Nancy, 1993 (Box 10)
    - Marker, Rita, 1993-1995 (Box 10)
    - Marks Lecture, 1990 (Box 10)
    - Marquis, Don, 1984 (Box 10)
    - Marshall, Burke, 1981-1985 (Box 10)
    - Marshall, Thurgood, 1984; 1987 (Box 10)
    - Martin, James, 1985-1986 (Box 10)
    - Martins, Mark, 1989 (Box 10)
    - Marx, Gary T., 1982-1983 (Box 10)
    - Marx, Paul, 1991 (Box 10)
    - Maryland Debate, 1980 (Box 10)
    - Maryland Journal of Contemporary Legal Issues, 1991 (Box 10)
    - Marzen, Thomas, 1993-1997 (Box 10)
    - Mason, Alpheus Thomas, 1979 (Box 10)
    - Massachusetts, University of, 1988 (Box 10)
    - Mathias Committee Papers, 1982 (Box 10)
    - Mauro, Robert L., 1989-1990 (Box 10)
    - Mauro, Tony, 1985-1991 (Box 10)
    - Maxman, Melissa, 1988-1990 (Box 10)
    - Mayo, Thomas, 1989-1990 (Box 10)
    - McCleskey Arguement, 1988 (Box 10)
    - McConnell, Mike, 1996-2001 (Box 10)
    - McCormick, Charles T., 1962-1963 (Box 10)
    - McCree, Wade, 1985-1987 (Box 10)
    - McDonald, Parker Lee, 1982 (Box 10)
    - McGovern, David T., 1983 (Box 10)
    - McGovern, George, 1972 (Box 10)
    - McKay, Robert B., 1982 (Box 10)
    - McMartin Case, 1990 (Box 10)
    - McWilliams, Carey, 1963 (Box 10)
    - Media, 1981 (Box 10)
    - Medicine, 1988 (Box 10)
    - Meilaender, Gilbert, 1993-1996 (Box 10)
    - Mello, Michael, 1997 (Box 10)
    - Memos, 1980-1985 (Box 10)
    - Menendez Brothers, 1994 (Box 10)
    - Mersky, Roy M., 1990; 1993 (Box 10)
    - Mertens, William, 1984 (Box 10)
    - Meyer, Bernard S., 1982 (Box 10)
    - Michigan Alumnus, 1984; undated (Box 10)
    - Michigan Bar Journal, 1993 (Box 10)
    - Michigan Center for Law Related Education, 1993 (Box 11)
    - Michigan Press, 1979-1992 (Box 11)
    - Miller, Arthur R., 1981-1994 (Box 11)
    - Miller, Merrill, 1982 (Box 11)
    - Miltenberg, Ned, 1985-1994 (Box 11)
    - Minan, John, 1985 (Box 11)
    - Minnesota Law Review, 1998 (Box 11)
    - Minnesota, University of, 1991-1995 (Box 11)
    - Minow, Martha, 1990-1991 (Box 11)
    - Miranda Op-Ed Pieces, 1985-1987 (Box 11)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1981-1982; 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Mitchell Lecture, 1977 (Box 11)
    - M'Naghten Case, 1982 (Box 11)
    - Modern Criminal Procedure, 1992-1994 (Box 11)
    - Mogill, Kenneth M., 1991-1994 (Box 11)
    - Mogin, Paul, 1981 (Box 11)
    - Monaghan, Henry P., 1982-1984 (Box 11)
    - Monahan, John, 1981 (Box 11)
    - Mondale, Walter F., 1962 (Box 11)
    - Mooney, Ralph, 1989 (Box 11)
    - Moore, W.S., 1981 (Box 11)
    - Moot Court, 1990 (Box 11)
    - Morris, Norval, 1974-1994 (Box 11)
    - Morrison, 1975 (Box 11)
    - Mortell, Jack, 1984 (Box 11)
    - MOVE, 1985 (Box 11)
    - Moylan, Charles E., 1981-1984 (Box 11)
    - Mueller, Gerhard O.W., 1960-1963 (Box 11)
    - Municipal League, undated (Box 11)
    - Murphy, Frank, 1968 (Box 11)
    - Murphy, State of Minnesota v., 1982-1983 (Box 11)
    - Muskegon Chronicle, 1989 (Box 11)
    - My Lai, 1971-1972 (Box 11)
  - N-Q
    - NACDL (National Association of Criminal Defense Lawyers), 1988 (Box 11)
    - Nagler, Stephen, 1989 (Box 11)
    - Napolitano, Janet, 1998 (Box 11)
    - Narain, Jagat, 1975 (Box 11)
    - Nation, The, 1995 (Box 11)
    - National College of District Attorneys, 1979 (Box 11)
    - National Institute for Trial Advocacy, 1989 (Box 11)
    - National Law Journal, 1981; 1989-1994 (Box 11)
    - National Practice Institute (NPI), 1981 (Box 11)
    - National Science Foundation, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
    - National Speakers' Forum, 1982 (Box 11)
    - NBC News, 1987-1992 (Box 11)
    - Necessity Killing, 1961-1993 (Box 11)
    - Neely, Richard, 1994 (Box 11)
    - NEH (National Endowment for the Humanities), 1987 (Box 11)
    - Nelson, Dorothy, 1987-1990 (Box 11)
    - Neuborne, Burt, 1990 (Box 11)
    - New Republic, 1989-1990 (Box 11)
    - New York Times, 1997 (Box 11)
    - New York Times Magazine, 1990-1993 (Box 11)
    - New York University, 1984 (Box 11)
    - Newbridge Communications, 1994-1995 (Box 11)
    - Newman, David, 1985 (Box 11)
    - News and Information Service (University of Michigan), 1981; 1989 (Box 11)
    - Newsday, 1972-1992 (Box 11)
    - Newspaper and Television, 1977-1980 (Box 11)
    - Newsweek, 1979-1993 (Box 11)
    - Nimmer, Melville, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Norris, Harold, 1982-1983 (Box 11)
    - Northwestern University, 1979-1985 (Box 11)
    - Norton, Martin L., 1991 (Box 11)
    - Notre Dame Journal of Law, Ethics and Public Policy, 1994 (Box 11)
    - Nowak, John E., 1981-1985 (Box 11)
    - Nussbaumer, John R., 1987 (Box 11)
    - Oakes, James L., 1983-1989 (Box 11)
    - Oberdorfer, Louis, 1988 (Box 11)
    - O'Connor, Mary, undated (Box 11)
    - O'Connor, Paul, 1989-1990 (Box 11)
    - O'Connor, Sandra Day, 1981-1991 (Box 11)
    - Odgers, S.J., 1983 (Box 11)
    - Oettinger, Elmer, 1981 (Box 11)
    - O'Flaherty, Hugh J., 1986 (Box 11)
    - Ogletree, Charles J., 1987-1991 (Box 11)
    - Ohio Northern University, 1985 (Box 11)
    - Ohio State Law Journal, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Oklahoma Law Review, 1992 (Box 11)
    - Oklahoma, University of, 1979-1992 (Box 11)
    - Olsen, Frances, 1990 (Box 11)
    - Opperman, Dodi, 1981-1983 (Box 11)
    - Oregon (Bradshaw), 1982-1983 (Box 11)
    - Orfield, Myron, 1987 (Box 11)
    - Orientation, 1977-1978 (Box 11)
    - Oster, Patrick, 1977 (Box 11)
    - Outlines, undated (Box 11)
    - Oxford Companion, 1991-1997 (Box 11)
    - Oxford Press, 2003 (Box 11)
    - Parker, Walter, 1984 (Box 11)
    - Palmer, Larry I., 1992 (Box 11)
    - Park, 1976 (Box 11)
    - Parole, 1987 (Box 11)
    - Paul, Robert, 1982 (Box 11)
    - Paulsen, Monrad, 1960 (Box 11)
    - Pease, Greg, 1989 (Box 11)
    - Penn, John Garrett, 1990 (Box 11)
    - Pentagon Papers, 1981 (Box 11)
    - Personnel Committee, 1999-2002 (Box 11)
    - Peterson, Edwin J., 1983 (Box 11)
    - Philadelphia Inquires, 1990-1991 (Box 12)
    - Phillips, J. Dickson, 1983 (Box 12)
    - Photographs (Kamisar), 1987; undated (Box 12)
    - Pickering, John (T. Dyk), 1994-1998 (Box 12)
    - Pitler, Robert, 1982-1994 (Box 12)
    - Pitofsky, Robert, 1985 (Box 12)
    - Pizzi, William, 1989 (Box 12)
    - Placement, 1984-1989 (Box 12)
    - Plagiarism, 1987 (Box 12)
    - Plaine, Herzel J.E., 1982 (Box 12)
    - Plants, J. Daniel, 1993 (Box 12)
    - Podell, Jack, 1982-1985 (Box 12)
    - Police Foundation, 1984-1985 (Box 12)
    - Police, Private, 1985-1996 (Box 12)
    - Pollack, Harriet, 1989 (Box 12)
    - Pollock, Stewart G., 1981-1989 (Box 12)
    - Polsby, Daniel D., 1984 (Box 12)
    - Poole, Cecil F., 1982 (Box 12)
    - Posner, Richard A., 1981-1983 (Box 12)
    - Powell, Lewis F., Jr., 1981-1987 (Box 12)
    - Pre-Law Information, undated (Box 12)
    - Pre-Trial Detainment, 1988 (Box 12)
    - Preventive Detention, 1987 (Box 12)
    - Princeton University, 1987 (Box 12)
    - Prison Project, 1982-1983 (Box 12)
    - Prisons, 1988-1990 (Box 12)
    - Privacy, 1991 (Box 12)
    - Probate, 1988 (Box 12)
    - Property Law, 1987 (Box 12)
    - Public Defender, 1985 (Box 12)
    - Publications and Activities, 1975-1987 (Box 12)
    - Puerto Rico, University of, 1990 (Box 12)
    - Purcell, Liz (BNA), 1984 (Box 12)
    - Pye, A. Kenneth, 1987 (Box 12)
    - Quill, Timothy, 1993-1995 (Box 12)
    - Quinlan, Karen Ann, 1975-1985; 4 folders (Box 12)
    - Quinn, John P., 1984 (Box 12)
    - Quotes, 1991 (Box 12)
  - R-S
    - Raab, Frances, 1989 (Box 12)
    - Rabinowitz, Jay, 1984-1986 (Box 12)
    - Ramsey, Paul, 1978 (Box 12)
    - Randolph, Philip, 1979 (Box 12)
    - Reed, John, 1987 (Box 12)
    - Regan, Don, 1981-1988 (Box 12)
    - Rehnquist, William H., 1985-1989 (Box 12)
    - Reichman, Victor, 1990 (Box 12)
    - Reilley, James W., 1983 (Box 12)
    - Remington, Frank, 1981-1982 (Box 12)
    - Renfrew, Allan, 1984 (Box 12)
    - Reprints, 1998-2003 (Box 12)
    - Research Assistants, 1973; 1991-1993 (Box 12)
    - Research Club of Michigan, 1988 (Box 12)
    - Research Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 12)
    - Retirement, 1999-2000 (Box 12)
    - Reuben, Richard, 1989-1992 (Box 12)
    - Reviews of Book, 1987 (Box 12)
    - Reynoso, Cruz, 1987 (Box 12)
    - Richey, Charles, 1994 (Box 12)
    - Richmond Newspapers, 1980-1982 (Box 12)
    - Rifle Association, 1983 (Box 12)
    - Right to Die, 1989-1990 (Box 12)
    - Riot (Detroit), 1967-1988 (Box 12)
    - Rivera, Rhonda R., 1983 (Box 12)
    - Riverside County, 1991 (Box 12)
    - Roadblocks, 1987 (Box 12)
    - Robbins, Ira P., 1982-1983 (Box 12)
    - Roberts, Samuel J., 1982 (Box 12)
    - Robertson, Pat, 1988 (Box 12)
    - Robinson, William P., 1982 (Box 12)
    - Roe v. Wade, 1985; 1989 (Box 12)
    - Rosenn, Max, 1984 (Box 12)
    - Rosenthal, A.M., 1989 (Box 12)
    - Rosenzveig, Ely J., 1986-1987 (Box 12)
    - Rosenzweig, Michael, 1986-1997 (Box 12)
    - Rotary Club, 1973 (Box 12)
    - Rotunda, Ronald, 1984-1994 (Box 12)
    - Royal Commission, 1977-1978 (Box 12)
    - Ruebhausen, Oscar, 1963-1964 (Box 12)
    - Ryan, James, 1999 (Box 12)
    - Sabbatical, 1988 (Box 12)
    - Safire, William, 1989 (Box 12)
    - Salerno Case, 1987 (Box 12)
    - Sales, Danforth, 1984 (Box 12)
    - SALT (Society of American Law Teachers), 1982 (Box 12)
    - San Diego, University of, 1998-2002 (Box 12)
    - San Francisco Barristers, 1987 (Box 12)